edwiseinternational.com 2015-06-12

# Study in UK, Study in USA Consultants, Study in UK from India, Study in Top University in Singapore, Study in Australia Consultants, Study in Canada University, Study Masters in France, Study in Universities of New Zealand, Study in Australia University, Study in Singapore University, Study in UK Consultants, Study in USA from India, Study in UK, Study in USA Consultants, Study in UK from India, Study in USA, Study in UK Consultants, Study in USA from India

Edwise Overseas Education Consultants is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. The Privacy of our customers & website visitors is our highest priority. Our relation with you is very precious & we realize the value of the information that you share with us.

Under no circumstances will we sell, disclose or rent to third parties, individually identifiable user information collected at our web site. We will solely use it to provide our services and as set forth in this privacy policy. 

From time to time, however, we may collect and/or disclose, transfer or share aggregated demographic or usage information obtained by us.Information collected by us includes your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and other information gathered through the applicable process. 

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy from time to time, without any prior notice. If we decide to substantially change the manner of collecting the information or use personally identifiable information, our members will be informed by e-mailing about the change in this Privacy Policy. 

However, your personal information will always be used in accordance with the privacy policy in effect, at the time, the information was collected.
